Guide to the Health Systems Agency of Southwestern Pennsylvania Records, 1971-1987 AIS.1987.02
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Projects, 1971-1987; I.
  - 551-Western Pennsylvania Hospital--Long Range Plan and Program for Development, 1977
  - 552-Braddock General Hospital--Fluoroscopic Unit, 1977 (Box 123)
  - 553-Community Mental Health Center of Beaver County--NIMH Federal Staffing Continuation Grant, 1977
  - 554-Twin Valley Convalescent Home--Eighty Bed Addition, 1977
  - 555-Hemophilia Center of Western Pennsylvania--Hemophilia Treatment Centers Program, 1977
  - 556-Miners Clinics/Russellton Medical Group--Application to National Health Service Corps, 1977
  - 557-University Health Center of Pittsburgh--Cardiac Catheterization Lab at Presbyterian Hospital, 1977
  - 558-Mid-Allegheny Clarion Valley Regional Health System--National Health Service Corps Application, 1977
  - 559-Latrobe Area Hospital--Replacement of X-ray Equipment, 1977
  - 560-Centerville Clinics--Rural Health Services, 1977
  - 561-Fayette County Mental Health/Mental Retardation Clinic--Continuation Application for the Fayette County Outreach to Children and Their Families, 1977
  - 562-Armstrong/Indiana Mental Health and Mental Retardation Program--Application for a Community Mental Health Center Planning Grant, 1977
  - 563-Dixmont State Hospital--Boiler Plant, 1977
  - 564-Dixmont State Hospital--Utility Distribution Center, 1977
  - 565-The Washington Hospital--ICU/CCU Equipment Replacement, 1977
  - 566-University Health Center-Presbyterian University Hospital--Dietary Department, 1977
  - 567-Westmoreland Manor--Renovation and Expansion, 1977
  - 568-University Health Center-Children's Hospital--Radiology Room Replacement, 1977
  - 569-University Health Center-Children's Hospital--Radiology Room Installed, 1977
  - 570-not present (Box 124)
  - 571-The Methodist Home--Addition, 1977
  - 572-Woodville State Hospital--Staff Development Program, 1977
  - 573-The South Side Hospital--Emergency Room Expansion and Renovation Project, 1977
  - 574-Human Services Center--Lawrence County Mental Health Center, 1977
  - 575-Mercy Hospital--Second Stage Replacement
  - 576-Shadyside Hospital--Procurement of Replacement and New Diagnostic Equipment, 1977
  - 577-Primary Care Health Services--Community Health Services Continuation Grant Application, 1977
  - 578-Canonsburg General Hospital--Ambulatory Care, 1978
  - 579-Canonsburg General Hospital--Nuclear Medicine, 1978
  - 580-Episcopal Church Home--New Facility, 1978
  - 581-University Health Center of Pittsburgh-Montefiore--CT Scanner, 1978
  - 582-Forbes Health System--New Health Maintenance Organization, 1978 (Box 125)
  - 583-University of Pittsburgh-Western Psychiatric Institute and Clinic--WPIC Renovation Project, 1977
  - 584-John J. Kane Hospital--Life Safety Code Renovations, 1977
  - 585-Jeannette District Memorial Hospital--Parking Garage, 1977
  - 586-South Side Hospital--Radioisotope Camera for the Division of Nuclear Medicine, 1977
  - 587-Suburban General Hospital--Boiler Conversion, 1977 (Box 126)
  - 588-St. John's General Hospital--JCAH and Life Safety Code Plan of Correction, 1977
  - 589-Armstrong County Health Center--Renovation Project, 1977
  - 590-Forbes Health System--Hospice Program, 1977
  - 591-St.Francis General Hospital--Diagnostic Radiology Equipment, 1978
  - 592-St.Francis General Hospital--Elevator Replacement, 1977
  - 593-South Hills Health System Community Mental Health/Mental Retardation Center--Continuation Staffing Grant, 1977
  - 594-St. Francis Community Mental Health/Mental Retardation Center--Adolescent and Children's Mental Health Staffing Grant, 1977
  - 595-Jameson Memorial Hospital--Window Replacement, 1977
  - 596-Suburban General Hospital--Air-conditioning in Central Building, 1977
  - 597-Forbes Health System--Family Practice Residency, 1977
  - 598-F.O.R. Sto Rox Neighborhood Health Council--Supplemental Health Service Grant, 1978 (Box 127)
  - 599-St. Clair Memorial Hospital--Telephone System, 1977
  - 600-Canonsburg General Hospital--HMO Feasibility Study Grant Application, 1977
  - 601-Community Human Services Corporation--Funding of Primary Health Care Station, 1977
  - 602-University of Pittsburgh School of Dental Medicine--Residency Training, 1977
  - 603-Western Pennsylvania Hospital--Dental General Practice Residency Grant Application, 1978
  - 604-Southern Indiana Health System--Application for Financial Assistance under the Rural Health Initiative Program, 1977
  - 605-Kiski Valley Medical Facility--Rural Health Initiative Funding, 1977
  - 606-McKeesport Hospital--Phase II Renovation and Expansion, 1978
  - 607-Butler Hospital--Operating Room Air Conditioning, 1978 (Box 128)
  - 608-Connellsville State Hospital--Dental Clinic for the Developmentally Disabled, 1978
  - 609-Redstone Presbytery--Construction of New Facility, 1978
  - 610-Allegheny General Hospital--General Dental Practice Residency, 1977
  - 611-Lexington Home for the Aged--New Facility, 1978
  - 612-Latrobe General Hospital--Modernization Expansion, 1978
  - 613-Southern Indiana Health System--Continuation Application for Financial Assistance, 1978 (Box 129)
  - 614-Graham's Nursing Home--Construction of 120 LTC Beds, 1978
  - 615-St. Francis General Hospital--Community Mental Health Center ARC Grant Request, 1978
  - 616-Mahoning Medical Center--ARC Continuation Grant Application for Primary Care Delivery System, 1978
  - 617-C. Howard Marcy State Hospital--Life Safety Code Renovation, 1978
  - 618-National Medical Care--Establishment of a 10-Station Affiliated Hemodialysis Unit in Westmoreland County, 1978
  - 619-Braddock General Hospital--Twenty-One Bed Critical Care Unit, 1978
  - 620-The South Side Hospital--Program for Development, 1978
  - 621-Latrobe Area Hospital--Boiler Plant Conversion, 1978 (Box 130)
  - 622-Torrance State Hospital--Boiler Plant Alterations, 1978
  - 623-Jewish Home and Hospital for the Aged--Additional Building, 1978
  - 624-Mid-Allegheny Clarion Valley Regional Health System--Rural Health Initiative Continuation Grant Application, 1978
  - 625-Family Planning Council--Continuation Application for Funding, 1978
  - 626-Latrobe Area Mental Health Center--Continuation Application Staffing Grant, 1978
  - 627-St. Clair Memorial Hospital--SMA II System, 1978
  - 628-St. Clair Memorial Hospital--Computer System, 1978
  - 629-Westmoreland Hospital Community-Mental Health Center--Continuation Staffing Grant Application, 1978
  - 630-South Hills Health System Home Health Agency--Respiratory Therapy in Service in Home Care Grant Application, 1978
  - 631-Emergency Medical Service Institute--Application for Funds, 1978
  - 632-Armstrong-Indiana County Drug and Alcohol Council--Proposed Annual County Plan for Treatment and Prevention of Drug and Alcohol Abuse, 1978
  - 633-Butler County Drug and Alcohol Council--Proposed Annual County Plan for Treatment and Prevention of Drug and Alcohol Abuse, 1978
  - 634-Forbes Health System--Facility Conversion at Pittsburgh to Long Term Care, 1978 (Box 131)
  - 635-Uiversity Health Center of Pittsburgh--Central Laboratory Information System, 1978
  - 636-Baptist Homes--Life Safety Code Renovations, 1978
  - 637-Presbyterian-University Hospital--CT Scanner, 1978
  - 638-Bernard I. Cohen, M.D.--Free Standing Ambulatory Surgical Center, 1978
  - 639-Connellsville State General Hospital--Intensive and Coronary Care Unit, 1978
  - 640-Washington-Greene Drug and Alcohol Planning Commission--County Plans on Drug and Alcohol Services, 1978
  - 641-not present
  - 642-Centerville Clinics-Community Mental Health Center--Continuation Staffing Grant Application, 1978 (Box 132)
  - 643-Shannock Valley Area Medical Facility--DHEW-RHI Planning and Development Grant, 1978
  - 644-West Haven Nursing Home--Twenty-Two Bed Addition, 1978
  - 645-Valley View Nursing Home of Kittanning--120 Bed Nursing Home, 1978
  - 646-Fayette County Mental Health/Mental Retardation Clinic--Continuation Application for the Fayette County Outreach to Children and Their Families, 1978
  - 647-Armstrong County Health Center-Primary Care Department, 1978
  - 648-St. Margaret Memorial Hospital--Medical Arts Building, 1978
  - 649-Hemophilia Center of Western Pennsylvania--Hemophilia Treatment Centers Program, 1978
  - 650-Fayette County Drug and Alcohol Commission--Fayette County Drug and Alcohol Plan, 1978
  - 651-St. Francis General Hospital Community Mental Health Center--Education Grant Proposal, 1978
  - 652-South Hills Health System Home Health Agency--Therapeutic Psychiatric Nursing in Home Care Grant Application, 1978
  - 653-Centerville Clinics--Community Health Centers Program Grant Application, 1978
  - 654-Mayview State Hospital--Water Distribution System and Renovations to Electrical System, 1978
  - 655-Mayview State Hospital--Renovations, 1978
  - 656-Community Mental Health Center of Beaver County--Federal Distress and Consultation and Education Grants, 1978
  - 657-Dixmont State Hospital--Air Conditioning Installation in Hutchinson Building, 1978
  - 658-Mon Valley Health and Welfare Council--Comprehensive Drug and Alcohol Service Delivery Plan for Westmoreland County, 1978
  - 659-Greene County Memorial Hospital--Home Health Services Grant Application, 1978 (Box 133)
  - 660-Community Medical Center of Northwest Washington County--Continuation Application for Rural Health Initiative Funds, 1978
  - 661-Sun City-East--Skilled, Intermediate and Custodial Nursing Facilities, 1978
  - 662-Kiski Valley Medical Facilities--Rural Health Initiative Continuation Funding Proposal, 1978
  - 663-Dixmont State Hospital--Renovations, 1978
  - 664-Southern Indiana Health Systems--Continuation Application for Funding, 1978
  - 665-South Hills Health System Community Mental Health/Mental Retardation Center--Consultation and Education Continuation Grant Application, 1978
  - 666-John J. Kane Hospital--Facility Replacement, 1978
  - 667-Southwestern Pennsylvania Economic Development District--Application for ARC Continuation Funding, 1978
  - 668-St.Clair Memorial Hospital--Life Safety Code Renovations, 1978
  - 669-X-U-N Diagnostic Associates--CT Scanner, 1978 (Box 134)
  - 670-Commissioner's Council on Drugs and Alcohol--Alcohol and Drug Abuse Diversion Project, 1978
  - 671-Elmcrest--60 Bed Addition, 1978
  - 672-Pennsylvania Blue Shield--Application for Computerized Tomography Scanner Installation, 1978
  - 673-Pennsylvania Blue Shield--Application for Computerized Tomography Scanner Installation, 1978
  - 674-Jashwant K. Sharma, M.D.--Renal Dialysis Center, 1978
  - 675-Citizen's General Hospital-KVMF--Transfer of Facility, 1978
  - 676-Miners Clinic--Operational Grant for the Rural Health Initiative/Community Health Centers Program, 1978
  - 677-South Hills Health System--Mental Health/Mental Retardation Continuation Staffing Grant Application, 1978 (Box 135)
  - 678-Penn Group Health Plan--Addition to West Haven Nursing Home, 1978
  - 679-Pennsylvania Department of Health--State Application for Influenza Immunization Project, 1978
  - 680-Citizens General Hospital--Renovations, 1978
  - 681-Commonwealth of Pennsylvania Department of Health--Genetic Disease Testing and Counseling Program, 1978
  - 682-Pinehurst Nursing and Convalescent Home--New Nursing Home, 1978
  - 683-Alma Illery Medical Center--Two Primary Care Centers, 1978
  - 684-Pennsylvania Department of Health-Bureau of Family Health Services--Improved Pregnancy Outcome Program, 1978
  - 685-not present
  - 686-Alma Illery Medical Center--Primary Care Health Services, Continuation Grant Application, 1978
  - 687-Armstong County Memorial Hospital--CAT Scanner, 1978
  - 688-Allegheny General Hospital--General Practice Residency in Dentistry, 1978 (Box 136)
  - 689-Western Pennsylvania Hospital--Residency Training in General Practice of Dentistry, 1978
  - 690-Alma Illery Medical Center-Satellite Clinic--Primary Care Health Services, 1978
  - 691-Bio-Medical Applications of Butler--Affiliated Maintenance Dialysis Unit, 1978
  - 692-St. Francis General Hospital--Purchase and Installation of Six MeV Linear Accelerators, 1978
  - 693-Presbyterian-University Hospital--ICU Monitoring Equipment, 1978
  - 694-The Western Pennsylvania Hospital--Expansion of Chronic Renal Program, 1978
  - 695-The Washington Hospital--CAT Scanner, 1978
  - 696-Harmarville Rehabilitation Center--Program and Development Proposal, 1978
  - 697-St. Francis General Hospital Mental Health/Mental Retardation Center--Adolescent and Children's Mental Health Continuation Staffing Grant, 1978
  - 698-Medical Center of Beaver County--Application to Provide Chronic Dialysis Services in Beaver County, 1978 (Box 137)
  - 699-Magee-Womens Hospital--Replacement of One Fluoroscopic Room, 1978
  - 700-The United Methodist Home--Life Safety Code Renovations
  - 701-Latrobe Area Mental Health Center--Continuing Education-Training Grant Application, 1978
  - 702-Medical Center of Beaver County--Radiation Therapy Unit, 1978
  - 703-Home Health Services of Allegheny County--Establishment, 1978
  - 704-The Country Place--New 120 Bed Nursing Home, 1978 (Box 138)
  - 705-Beaver Valley Geriatric Center--Replacement of Two Burners, 1978
  - 706-Westmoreland Hospital Community Mental Health Center--Operational Grant Application, 1978
  - 707-The Community Mental Health Center of Beaver County--National Institute on Alcohol Abuse and Alcoholism Demonstration Grant, 1978
  - 708-Indiana Hospital--Telephone Transmission Service for EEG, 1978
  - 709-Butler County Memorial Hospital--New Facility, 1978
  - 710-Southeastern Greene Community Health Center--National Health Service Corps Personnel, 1978
  - 711-Pennsylvania Department of Health--Venereal Disease Control Program Grant Application, 1978
  - 712-Commonwealth of Pennsylvania-Department of Health--Influenza Immunization Program, 1978
  - 713-Aliquippa Hospital--ESRD Program, 1978
  - 714-Allegheny County Health Department-Immunization Project, 1978 (Box 139)
  - 715-Valley View Nursing Home--Expansion, 1979
  - 716-Westmoreland Hospital Association--Telephone System Replacement, 1978
  - 717-University of Pittsburgh School of Nursing--Nurse Practitioner/Clinician Program, 1978
  - 718-Department of Health--Communicable Disease Control in Pennsylvania Continuation Grant Application, 1978
  - 719-Suburban General Hospital--Lab Equipment Acquisition, 1978
  - 720-Allegheny County Health Department--1979 Federal Rodent Control/Neighborhood Improvement Program Proposal, 1978
  - 721-Shadyside Hospital--Construction of Medical Office Building and Additional Parking Facilities, 1978
  - 722-Windsor House--New 168 Bed LTC Facility, 1978
  - 723-Greene County Memorial Hospital--Ultrasound, 1978
  - 724-Southern Indiana Health System--Continuation Funding Application, 1979
  - 725-Community College of Allegheny College--CCAC Physician Assistant Program Training Grant Association, 1979
  - 726-Oakmont Residence--39 LTC Bed Addition, 1979 (Box 140)
  - 727-Westmoreland Home Health Care Agency--Hospice Demonstration Grant Application, 1979
  - 728-Mountain View Center for Rehabilitation and Convalescent Care--Addition of 48 Skilled Nursing Care Beds, 1979
  - 729-Community Health Clinic--Community Health Clinic Project, 1979
  - 730-Southside Hospital--Program for Development, 1979
  - 731-Turtle Creek Valley Mental Health/Mental Retardation--Initial Operations Grant, 1979 (Box 141)
  - 732-Lancer Development Corporation--Intermediate Care Facility/Mental Retardation Facility, 1979
  - 733-Allegheny East Mental Health and Mental Retardation Center--Application for Community Mental Health Center, 1979
  - 734-Centerville Clinics--Community Health Centers Program Continuing Grant Application, 1979 (Box 142)
  - 735-United Mental Health--Alcohol Abuse Program-Residential Care, 1979
  - 736-Vincentian Home for Chronically Ill--Expansion, 1979
  - 737-Citizens General Hospital--Training Allied Health Professionals for Alle-Kisk Valley Grant Application, 1979
  - 738-Irene Stacy Community Mental Health Center--Continuation Application Federal Staffing Grant, 1979
  - 739-Westmoreland Hospital Association--Elevator Installation, 1979
  - 740-Forbes Health System--Family Practice Residence Program Continuation Grant Support, 1979
  - 741-Forbes Health System-Satellite Family Practice Center at Columbia Health Center--Supplemental Grant Support, 1979
  - 742-Emergency Medical Service Institute--Advanced Life Support Planning Activities in Rural Counties of Southwestern Pennsylvania Grant Application, 1979
  - 743-Monongahela Valley Hospital--CT Scanner, 1979
  - 744-Mid-Allegheny Clarion Valley Regional Health System--Rural Health Initiative Grant Application, 1979
  - 745-Mahoning Medical Center--Continuation Grant Application, 1979
  - 746-Community College of Allegheny County--Associate Degree Career Ladder Nursing Education Program, 1979
  - 747-County of Butler Commissioners' Council on Drugs and Alcohol--Drug and Alcohol Program for Butler County Prison, 1979
  - 748-Forbes Health System-Columbia Health Center--Replace Operating Room Air Conditioning, 1979
  - 749-Forbes Health Maintenance Plan--Continuation Grant, 1979
  - 750-Westmoreland Hospital Association--Community Mental Health Center Operational Grant Application, 1979 (Box 143)
  - 751-West Greene Health Services--Primary Health Care Grant Application, 1979
  - 752-McKeesport Hospital--Dialysis Center, 1979
  - 753-County of Allegheny--Annual Plan and Budget for Drugs and Alcohol, 1979
  - 754-Washington-Greene County Mental Health/Mental Retardation Program--Annual Plan for Services, 1979
  - 755-Health and Welfare Planning Association--Community Health Information System Study, 1979
  - 756-Armstrong-Indiana County D & A Commission--Proposed Annual Plan for the Treatment of and Prevention of Drugs and Alcohol, 1979
  - 757-Family Planning Council of Western Pennsylvania--Family Planning Services Continuation Grant Application, 1979
  - 758-West Haven Nursing Home--83 LTC Bed Expansion, 1979
  - 759-F.O.R. Sto-Rox Neighborhood Health Council-Neighborhood Family Health Center--Urban Health Initiative Continuation Grant Application, 1979
  - 760-Canonsburg General Hospital--Program for Development, 1979 (Box 144)
  - 761-Verland Foundation--60 Bed ICF/MR Facility, 1979
  - 762-Allegheny Valley School--Garage/Warehouse Construction, 1979
  - 763-Northwest Pennsylvania Regional Planning and Development Commission--Regional Emergency Communications System Grant Application, 1979 (Box 145)
  - 764-Shannock Valley Area Medical Facility--Operational Grant Application, 1979
  - 765-Commonwealth of Pennsylvania--Statewide Sudden Infant Death Syndrome, Information and Counseling Program, 1979
  - 766-St. Clair Memorial Hospital--New Parking Lot, 1979
  - 767-Forbes Health System-East Suburban Health Center--CT Scanner, 1979
  - 768-Pennsylvania Department of Health--Childhood Accident Prevention Program Grant Application, 1979
  - 769-Shadyside Hospital--Cardiac Care Lab, 1979
  - 770-University Health Center--Additional Computer for Central Data Center, 1979
  - 771-South Hills Health System--Intermediate Care Facility for the Mentally Retarded, 1979
  - 772-Sickle Cell Society--Comprehensive Service Program Grant Application, 1979 (Box 146)
  - 773-St. Francis General Hospital--Information System, 1979
  - 774-St. Francis General Hospital--Energy Conservation Equipment, 1979
  - 775-Fayette County Mental Health/Mental Retardation Clinic--Outreach to Children and their Families Continuation Grant Application, 1979
  - 776-Centerville Clinics--Community Mental Health Center Continuation Grant Application, 1979
  - 777-Community Mental Health Center of Allegheny/Indiana Counties--Initial Operations Grant, 1979
  - 778-Pennsylvania Department of Health--Genetic Disease Testing and Counseling Services Program Continuation Grant
  - 779-St. Francis General Hospital Community Mental Health Center--Parent-Infant Program, 1979
  - 780-St. Francis General Hospital Community Mental Health Center--Consultation and Education Program Grant Application, 1979 (Box 147)
  - 781-Chartiers Mental Health/Mental Retardation Center--Community Mental Health Center Initial Operations Grant Application, 1979
  - 782-Grandview Health Care-Fayette County--120-Bed LTC Facility, 1979
  - 783-Community Medical Center of Northwest Washington County--Rural Health Initiative Continuation Grant Application, 1979
  - 784-South Hills Health System Community Mental Health/Mental Retardation Center--Children's Services Continuation Grant Application, 1979
  - 785-South Hills Health System Community Mental Health/Mental Retardation Center--Consultation and Education Continuation Grant Application, 1979
  - 786-Mon Valley Health and Welfare Council--Mon Valley Ambulatory Care Center Project Continuation Grant Application, 1979
  - 787-Nurse Consultation and Service Agency--Expansion of Services for an Existing Home Health Agency Grant Application, 1979
  - 788-Forbes Health Maintenance Plan-HMO Loan Application, 1979
  - 789-University of Pittsburgh School of Nursing--Primary Care Nursing of Infants and Children Continuation Grant, 1979
  - 790-Consilium--Project Alcohol and the Elderly Grant Application, 1979
  - 791-South Hills Health System Home Health Agency--Respiratory Therapy Service in Home Care Continuation Grant Application, 1979 (Box 148)
  - 792-Pennsylvania Department of Health--Black Lung Clinics Program Grant Application, 1979
  - 793-North Hills Passavant Hospital--Installation of a Laboratory Computer System, 1979
  - 794-Jameson Memorial Hospital--Modernization and Bed Replacement, 1979
  - 795-American Medical Affiliates--New Nursing Home in North Versailles Township, 1979
  - 796-Lutheran Welfare Concordia Home--Addition of 60 ICF Beds, 1979 (Box 149)
  - 797-Ellwood City Hospital--Program for Expansion and Renovation, 1979
  - 798-Allegheny County Health Department--Influenza Immunization Continuation Grant Application, 1979
  - 799-Southwestern Pennsylvania Economic Development District--Human Resources Development Continuation Grant Application, 1979
  - 800-Forbes Health Maintenance Plan--Continuation Grant Application, 1979
  - 801-St. Francis Hospital of New Castle--Program for Development, 1979
  - 802-Pennsylvania Department of Health--High Blood Pressure Control Program Grant Application, 1979
  - 803-Alma Illery Medical Center-Primary Care Health Services--Continuation Grant Application, 1979
  - 804-Miners Clinics--Rural Health Initiative/Community Health Centers Program Continuation Grant Application, 1979
  - 805-Western Psychiatric Institute and Clinic--Life Safety Code Renovations, 1979 (Box 150)
  - 806-Centerville Clinics--Rural Health Initiative Continuation Grant Application, 1979
  - 807-Centerville Clinics--Supplemental RHI Adolescent Health Services Grant Application, 1979
  - 808-Centerville Clinics--Supplemental RHI, Ambulatory Health Care and Community Mental Health Care Linkage Program, 1979
  - 809-Bio-Medical Applications of Pittsburgh--Change of Site, 1979
  - 810-Indiana Hospital--Renovation of Existing Nurses Residence and Classroom Building into a Medical Office Building, 1979
  - 811-Pennsylvania Department of Health--Health Education/Risk Reduction Program, 1979
  - 812-Butler County Memorial Hospital--CT Scanner, 1979
  - 813-Jeanette District Memorial Hospital--Replace Radiographic Units, 1979
  - 814-Presbyterian-University Hospital--Expand Ultrasound Services, 1979
  - 815-Presbyterian-University Hospital--Artificial Kidney Treatment Center, 1979
  - 816-Forbes Health System--Graduate Training in Family Medicine Continuation Grant, 1979
  - 817-Monsour Medical Center--Graduate Training Program in Family Medicine Grant, 1979
  - 818-American Medical Affiliates-Wesley Manor Health Care Center-120 Bed Long Term Care Facility, 1979